Fatima Romagnoli Mecenas –Seattle-WA

fatinhadorei@hotmail.com - 425-761-2190

I am highly motivated for learning and assisting others to succeed. I am known for positive attitude and flexibility which I attribute to my experience in the creative field as well as to my experience working in offices. I am reliable and excellent in multitasking when needed to handle high volume of assignments in an organization including knowledge of legal procedures.

SKILLS

- Managing schedules
- Handling sensitive information with discretion and according to best practices
- Communicating verbally and in writing with clients and team members
- Trilingual fluency (English, Portuguese, and Spanish)
- Conducting research using academic databases, books, and periodicals
- Client-focused, computer-savvy

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Position/ Company - Real Estate Agent/Gurnee and Associates Real Estate – May/2018-present

- Assisting buyers to find properties, negotiate the deal, and handle paperwork
- Assisting sellers get ready the home for sale, determine the sales prices and negotiate the
- Collaborating with other agents to facilitate leads in Spanish
- Developing partnership with loan officers and educate clients regarding special loan programs

Position/ Company - Marketing Manager / Agency Doors - DATA 2018- to date

- Overseeing all market efforts of the company
- Brainstorming ideas for branding and campaigns
- Analyzing results for future use
- Leading meetings to expand the company overseas
- Facilitating business between Brazil and the Unites States that resulted in 10% growth in reaching out new customers

Position/ Company - Producer and Lead Role Actress/ Brazilian Arts Performance Center - 2015 – to date

- Managing business responsibilities including finding the venue location
- Overseeing the project from development through post-production
- Managing the marketing campaign for a theater play at Kirkland Performance Center that resulted in 100% of tickets sold

Position/ Company - Office Manager/ Four Seasons Cleaning-September 2017- February 2018

- Preparing operational reports and schedules to ensure efficiency on using the company fleet
- Monitoring and maintaining office supplies inventory
- Designing and implementing office system that optimized the time, saving the employees 30 min per day on organizing supplies
- Handling customer inquiries and complaints
- Managing internal staff relations

Position/ Company - Office Manager - Capital Builders Inc -

- Allocating available resources to enable successful task performance
- Coordinating schedules, appointments and bookings
- Developing a marketing plan that introduced the company on the digital marketing witch increased the leads generation in 30%.
- Designing and implementing office policies and procedures
- Employee Scheduling and payroll

Position/ Company - Law Assistant / Jairo Britto Social Security Law office/ Brazil 2003-2004

- Managing of process, preparation of legal documents and court filings
- Preparing legal documents in judicial and administrative proceedings
- Drafting, analyzing, and reviewing contracts utilized in the day to day business of clients. Researching regard various labor and social security issues to provide the best solution for the clients

Position/ Company - Law Clerk Internship/ Joao Ferreira Law Office Brazil 2001-2003

- Preparing of opinions and comments on business practices utilized by the client company based upon legal analysis, applicable legal statues, and requirements of regulatory bodies.
- Creating of contracts, addendums, term and agreements, meeting minutes, and client intake forms.
- Mediation extrajudicial negotiations.

CERTIFICATION:

WA-Real Estate License #135088

EDUCATION:

• Major in Law - 4 years of undergraduate study at a regionally accredited institution-WES Institution/Dates

Maringa State University, Brazil - 2001-2004

• Real Estate Education - 90 hours Seattle, WA – May 2018

Bookkeeping November 2015- Everett Community College